const QuestionBank = {


    Entertainment: [
        {
            question: "Which rapper is popular known as wizzy?",
            answers: ["Jay z", "Young jeezy", "Wizkid", "Lil wayne"],
            correct: "Lil wayne",
            questionId: "049099"
        },
        {
            question: "Which niegrian musician is referred to as Baddo?",
            answers: ["Wizkid", "Sam Loco", "Davido", "Olamide"],
            correct: "Olamide",
            questionId: "099093"
        },
        {
            question: "What is the real name of the actor that plays the hero 'iron man'?",
            answers: ["Robert downey jnr", "Brad pitt", "Leonardo d'caprio", "Johnny depp"],
            correct: "Robert downey jnr",
            questionId: "091099"
        },
        {
            question: "Which nollywood actor made the movie Lion Heart?",
            answers: ["Rita dominic", "Genevieve", "Funke akindele", "Desmond eliot"],
            correct: "Genevieve",
            questionId: "096099"
        },
        {
            question: "Simi is married to which nigerian musician?",
            answers: ["Adekunle Gold", "Davido", "Ramsey Noah", "Burna boy"],
            correct: "Adekunle Gold",
            questionId: "091299"
        },     {
            question: "Which niegrian musician sang a popular song Titled Pana?",
            answers: ["Falz", "Wizkid", "Tekno", "Kiss Daniel"],
            correct: "Tekno",
            questionId: "099099"
        },
    ],
    General: [
        {
            question:
                "Nigeria's location in Africa is?",
            answers: ["North coast", "West coast", "East coast", "Land-locked central"],
            correct: "West coats",
            questionId: "093909"
        },
        {
            question:
                "What organ in the body suffer when you don't drink enough water",
            answers: ["Heart", "Lungs", "Kidney", "Brain"],
            correct: "Kidney",
            questionId: "009039"
        },
        {
            question:
                "What OS does samsung phones use?",
            answers: ["Android", "IOS", "Windows", "Ubuntu"],
            correct: "Android",
            questionId: "090089"
        },
    ],
    Politics: [
        {
            question:
                "When did Nigeria gain her Independence?",
            answers: ["October 1st, 2004", "October 1st, 1960", "October 1st, 1961", "October 1st, 2007"],
            correct: "October 1st, 1960",
            questionId: "01010101"
        },
        {
            question:
                "How old was Michael Taiwo Akinkunmi when he designed the Nigerian flag?",
            answers: ["23 years old", "40 years old", "22 years old", "50 years old"],
            correct: "23 years old",
            questionId: "01010321"
        },
        {
            question:
                "Who was the first Prime Minister of Nigeria after independence?",
            answers: ["Alhaji Shehu Shagari", "Dr. Nnamdi Azikiwe", "Abubakar Tafawa Balewa", "Fela Anikulapo Ransome-Kuti"],
            correct: "Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
            questionId: "092299"
        },
        {
            question:
                "Who was the first President of Nigeria?",
            answers: ["General Muhammadu Buhari", "Dr. Nnamdi Azikiwe", "Dapo Oyebanji", "Abubakar Tafawa Balewa"],
            correct: "Dr. Nnamdi Azikiwe",
            questionId: "099099"
        },

    ],
    Trivia: [
        {
            question:
                "how build the app ?",
            answers: ["vinayak", "sarthak", "somil", "devesh"],
            correct: "vinayak",
            questionId: "099099"
        },
        {
            question:
                "how build the app ?",
            answers: ["vinayak", "sarthak", "somil", "devesh"],
            correct: "vinayak",
            questionId: "099099"
        },
        {
            question:
                "how build the app ?",
            answers: ["vinayak", "sarthak", "somil", "devesh"],
            correct: "vinayak",
            questionId: "09459099"
        },
        {
            question:
                "how build the app ?",
            answers: ["vinayak", "sarthak", "somil", "devesh"],
            correct: "vinayak",
            questionId: "0912219099"
        },
    ]

}


export default QuestionBank